[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[Hello There]
[أهلاً بك]
[Episode 8]
[الحلقة 8]
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
I didn't find the source of the Wushan rumors.
لم أجد مصدر شائعات وشان.
But I heard
لكني سمعت
the assistant manager of Fengming Pavilion, Jin Badou,
مساعد مدير Fengming Pavilion ، Jin Badou ،
has arrived at Xuanqi Mountain.
وصل إلى جبل Xuanqi.
Maybe we can buy information from him.
ربما يمكننا شراء المعلومات منه.
Okay.
تمام.
Zhi, go with Ruoyu.
زهي ، اذهب مع رويو.
Yes.
نعم.
Young Master, there's one more thing.
السيد الشاب ، هناك شيء آخر.
The martial artists who demanded for the Wushan yesterday
فنانو الدفاع عن النفس الذين طالبوا بالوشان أمس
haven't left the mountain yet.
لم يغادر الجبل بعد.
They are waiting outside the gate.
إنهم ينتظرون خارج البوابة.
They bribed the servants
قاموا برشوة الخدم
and want to sneak in to steal the Wushan.
وتريد التسلل لسرقة ووشان.
They refused to accept the real Wushan when it was offered to them,
لقد رفضوا قبول Wushan الحقيقي عندما عرض عليهم ،
yet they insist on stealing it.
ومع ذلك يصرون على سرقتها.
Those idiots.
هؤلاء البلهاء.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
we'll end them once and for all.
سننهيها مرة واحدة وإلى الأبد.
Miss Tang, do you have any ideas?
آنسة تانغ ، هل لديك أي أفكار؟
Wait.
انتظر.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Why are you sneaking around?
لماذا تتسلل؟
Brother.
شقيق.
My cousin's grandaunt's
حفيدة ابن عمي
grandson's aunt's intimate friend
صديق عمة حفيد الحميم
works as a servant in Xuanqi Mountain.
يعمل كخادم في جبل Xuanqi.
He just told me
لقد قال لي للتو
that Wushan grows behind the mountain
أن Wushan ينمو خلف الجبل
and will mature tonight.
وسوف تنضج الليلة.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Is your news reliable?
هل أخبارك موثوقة؟
I'm the Black Wind's Little Tyrant.
أنا طاغية الريح الأسود الصغير.
Of course my news is reliable.
بالطبع أخباري موثوقة.
The details about your relative
التفاصيل حول قريبك
seem to have changed.
يبدو أنه قد تغير.
Have they changed?
هل تغيروا؟
Have they not?
أليس كذلك؟
Don't mind these trivial details.
لا تهتم بهذه التفاصيل التافهة.
The Wushan is the priority.
Wushan هي الأولوية.
That makes sense.
منطقي.
Let's go steal the Wushan today.
دعنا نذهب لسرقة Wushan اليوم.
Look.
نظرة.
This Wushan I've made is so exquisite
هذا Wushan الذي صنعته رائع للغاية
those scumbag martial artists
هؤلاء الفنانين القتاليين scumbag
will never forget this.
لن ننسى هذا ابدا.
It does look like a miraculous medicine.
يبدو أنه دواء معجزة.
But why does it have such a weird smell?
لكن لماذا لها مثل هذه الرائحة الغريبة؟
After all, Yun Gaixue
بعد كل شيء ، يون Gaixue
personally doused this radish with manure.
صب هذا الفجل شخصيا مع السماد.
I'll add some more bitter gourd juice.
سأضيف المزيد من عصير القرع المر.
That's perfect.
هذا ممتاز.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Why does I feel so weak?
لماذا أشعر بضعف شديد؟
Did someone poison me?
هل سممني أحد؟
But I have to say
لكن علي أن أقول
that you're too rough with Yun Gaixue.
أنك قاسي جدًا مع Yun Gaixue.
Even I'm shocked.
حتى أنا مصدومة.
I'm not as extreme as you.
أنا لست متطرفًا مثلك.
The way you're making this medicine
الطريقة التي تصنع بها هذا الدواء
looks quite disgusting.
يبدو مقرف جدا.
Ugly monster.
وحش قبيح.
How dare you try to poison me?
كيف تجرؤ على محاولة تسممي؟
I'll destroy you.
سأدمرك.
Xue.
Xue.
Brother, bad news!
أخي ، أخبار سيئة!
The ugly monster and this man are trying to kill us.
الوحش القبيح وهذا الرجل يحاولان قتلنا.
This is Physician Yan.
هذا هو الطبيب يان.
He's here to treat you.
إنه هنا ليعالجك.
He won't hurt you.
لن يؤذيك.
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
Are you bewitched by the ugly monster?
هل يسحرك الوحش القبيح؟
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
As long as I'm here,
طالما أنا هنا ،
you won't be able to attack Xuanqi Mountain.
لن تكون قادرًا على مهاجمة جبل Xuanqi.
Stop messing around.
توقف عن العبث.
Focus on cooperating with Physician Yan for your treatment.
ركز على التعاون مع الطبيب يان في علاجك.
Go to sleep.
اذهب إلى النوم.
Physician Yan,
الطبيب يان
please take care of my brother.
من فضلك اعتني بأخي.
The Wushan is ready.
ووشان جاهز.
Let's prepare for the next step.
دعنا نستعد للخطوة التالية.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
The great devil is awake.
الشيطان العظيم مستيقظ.
How dare you do this to me?
كيف تجرؤ على فعل هذا بي؟
When I can move,
عندما أستطيع التحرك ،
your corpse will be so disfigured nobody will know it's you.
ستكون جثتك مشوهة للغاية ولن يعرف أحد أنها أنت.
I really want to cut open your head
أريد حقًا أن أفتح رأسك
to see what it looks like inside.
لنرى كيف يبدو الداخل.
You want to cut open my head?
تريد فتح رأسي؟
Why are you holding a spoon?
لماذا تمسك بالملعقة؟
Do you really want to take my brain?
هل تريد حقًا أن تأخذ عقلي؟
Don't you know
لا تعرف
strange doctors like me
أطباء غريبون مثلي
like exotic food,
مثل الأطعمة الغريبة ،
especially the ones we've just dissected?
خاصة تلك التي قمنا بتشريحها للتو؟
Sprinkle some cumin
يرش بعض الكمون
and some salt and pepper.
وبعض الملح والفلفل.
Then, scoop up a mouthful
ثم تناول ملعقة صغيرة
and you will experience a subtle
وسوف تواجه خفية
and lively
وحيوية
taste.
التذوق.
You lunatic! Even if I become a ghost,
أنت مجنون!  حتى لو أصبحت شبحًا ،
I will come back to kill you.
سأعود لقتلك.
I'm so scared.
أنا خائف جدا.
But you can't move now.
لكن لا يمكنك التحرك الآن.
How can you deal with me?
كيف يمكنك التعامل معي؟
You lunatic!
أنت مجنون!
If you're so fearless, don't leave. Come back!
إذا كنت لا تعرف الخوف ، فلا تغادر.  عد!
Great devil of Xuanqi Mountain?
الشيطان العظيم لجبل Xuanqi؟
All he can do
كل ما يستطيع فعله
is making threats.
يقوم بالتهديدات.
Empty threats!
تهديدات فارغة!
Right? And they said this place is heavily guarded
حق؟  وقالوا إن هذا المكان شديد الحراسة
and impenetrable?
ولا يمكن اختراقها؟
I think Xuanqi Mountain
أعتقد جبل Xuanqi
is not even as good as our Black Wind Fortress' little hill.
ليست جيدة مثل التل الصغير في قلعة الريح السوداء.
It's a hike.
إنه ارتفاع.
Look here.
انظر هنا.
This won't do either.
هذا لن يفعل أي منهما.
They are looking down on me.
إنهم ينظرون إلي بإزدراء.
No.
رقم.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
What's the difference?
ماهو الفرق؟
How dare you look down on us!
كيف تجرؤ على النظر إلينا باستخفاف!
Fine.
بخير.
In a moment, you'll experience
في لحظة ، ستختبر
the multitude of traps I've prepared for you.
العديد من الفخاخ التي أعددتها لك.
Let's see if you still can laugh then.
دعنا نرى ما إذا كان لا يزال بإمكانك الضحك بعد ذلك.
If they fall into a trap
إذا وقعوا في الفخ
and get suspicious,
والشك ،
what should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
One never knows how to cherish things
لا يعرف المرء كيف يعتز بالأشياء
that are easily obtained.
التي يمكن الحصول عليها بسهولة.
Instead, things are only regarded as precious
بدلاً من ذلك ، تعتبر الأشياء ثمينة فقط
if they are laboriously obtained.
إذا تم الحصول عليها بشق الأنفس.
Just wait and see.
فقط انتظر وانظر.
What great devil of Xuanqi Mountain?
ما هو الشيطان العظيم لجبل Xuanqi؟
Not only does he make threats,
لا يقوم فقط بتوجيه التهديدات ،
but also plays dirty.
ولكن أيضا يلعب قذرة.
I, Black Wind...
أنا ، الريح السوداء ...
I, Black Wind's Big Tyrant,
أنا ، طاغية بلاك ويند الكبير ،
despise them from the bottom of my heart.
احتقرهم من اعماق قلبي.
That's right. He even set up traps.
صحيح.  حتى أنه نصب الفخاخ.
He's more sinister than us.
إنه أكثر شرا منا.
What great devil?
أي شيطان عظيم؟
Big whoop!
نعيق كبيرة!
Is that the Wushan?
هل هذا هو وشان؟
We've traveled across much land and water,
لقد سافرنا عبر الكثير من الأراضي والمياه ،
and encountered many obstacles.
وواجه العديد من العقبات.
Brother,
شقيق،
this has been tough.
كان هذا صعبًا.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
They're so pitiful.
إنهم يرثى لهم.
They just wanted to steal some Wushan.
لقد أرادوا فقط سرقة بعض Wushan.
Did I go too far?
هل ذهبت بعيدا جدا؟
I'm a little regretful...
أنا أشعر بالأسف قليلاً ...
regretful that I wasn't harsher.
يؤسفني أنني لم أكن أقسى.
If I knew it was going to be this fun,
إذا كنت أعلم أنها ستكون ممتعة ،
I would have set up more levels of traps.
كنت سأقوم بإعداد المزيد من مستويات الفخاخ.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
This must be delicious.
يجب أن يكون هذا لذيذ.
Brother,
شقيق،
why does the Wushan have such a stench?
لماذا هذه الرائحة النتنة لوشان؟
It's similar to the stench in the latrine.
إنها تشبه الرائحة الكريهة في المرحاض.
That stench.
تلك الرائحة النتنة.
Is it?
فعلا؟
A little.
القليل.
Think about your body odor.
فكر في رائحة جسمك.
Stop talking and eat quickly.
توقف عن الكلام وتناول الطعام بسرعة.
Brother,
شقيق،
did you hear something?
هل سمعت شيئا؟
Why are you so...
لماذا أنت شديد ال...
Fine, let's go.
حسنًا ، دعنا نذهب.
I heard something.
انا سمعت شيئا.
Hurry.
عجل.
It's time for my performance.
حان الوقت لأدائي.
How dare you break into Xuanqi Mountain at this late hour
كيف تجرؤ على اقتحام جبل Xuanqi في هذه الساعة المتأخرة
and eat our only Wushan?
وأكل وشان فقط لدينا؟
Spit it out!
ألفظه، أبصقها أبصق عليها!
Stop right there now!
توقف هناك الآن!
Stop right there!
توقف هناك!
Let's go!
هيا بنا!
Bad news!
اخبار سيئة!
The only real Wushan was stolen by the Black Wind's Double Tyrants!
سُرق ووشان الحقيقي الوحيد من قبل طغاة الريح السوداء المزدوجة!
What?
لما؟
I was guarding here all night.
كنت أحرس هنا طوال الليل.
They actually stole it?
فعلا سرقوها؟
What?
لما؟
How dare the Black Wind's Double Tyrants act so selfishly
كيف يجرؤ طغاة الريح السوداء المزدوجة على التصرف بأنانية
and steal the Wu-Wu-Wushan?
وسرقة وو وو وشان؟
W-W-Where are th-they?
WW- أين هم ال؟
They went that way. Go after them!
ذهبوا بهذه الطريقة.  اذهب ورائهم!
H-H-Hurry! Go after them!
HH- على عجل!  اذهب ورائهم!
Catch them!
قبض عليهم!
Go!
اذهب!
Brother.
شقيق.
I feel like my inner energy is swirling
أشعر أن طاقتي الداخلية تدور
fiercely and vigorously.
بضراوة وقوة.
I can fight for three days and three nights, nonstop.
يمكنني القتال لمدة ثلاثة أيام وثلاث ليالٍ دون توقف.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
Wushan really is a miraculous medicine.
وشان حقا دواء معجز.
-Only those who've tried it will know. -They're here. Come on.
- فقط أولئك الذين جربوه سيعرفون.  -انهم هنا.  تعال.
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
Run!
يركض!
Wait, why do we need to run?
انتظر ، لماذا نحتاج للركض؟
I don't know. It's my occupational habit acting up. Let's just run.
لا أعلم.  إنها عادتي المهنية في التصرف.  دعنا فقط نركض.
-Wushan, where are you? -Hurry.
وشان اين انت؟  -عجل.
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
Quickly.
بسرعة.
Keep up with them.
مواكبة معهم.
The Wushan rumor is fake.
إشاعة ووشان كاذبة.
There's no one real Wushan.
لا يوجد وشان حقيقي واحد.
Those idiots.
هؤلاء البلهاء.
They were fooled by Li Chengxi.
لقد خدعهم Li Chengxi.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Useless!
عديم الفائدة!
How dare you instigate everyone to steal Wushan?
كيف تجرؤ على تحريض الجميع على سرقة وشان؟
You can't even accomplish a small task like this.
لا يمكنك حتى إنجاز مهمة صغيرة كهذه.
I'll call them back.
سأتصل بهم مرة أخرى.
No need.
لا حاجة.
These people are of no use now.
هؤلاء الناس لا فائدة لهم الآن.
I've set a trap on the mountain.
لقد نصبت فخًا على الجبل.
You just need to lure Li Chengxi into the trap.
أنت فقط بحاجة إلى إغراء Li Chengxi في الفخ.
You must make sure he is hit hard this time
يجب عليك التأكد من تعرضه لضربة قوية هذه المرة
and get the Book of Yueque.
واحصل على كتاب Yueque.
Yes.
نعم.
Those bastards who coveted Wushan
هؤلاء الأوغاد الذين اشتهوا ووشان
are finally lured away.
أخيرًا تم إغراؤهم بعيدًا.
I can finally sleep well.
يمكنني أخيرا أن أنام جيدا.
But
لكن
who instigated this commotion?
من الذي أثار هذه الفوضى؟
I've asked Zhi and Ruoyu to go down the mountain to investigate.
لقد طلبت من Zhi و Ruoyu النزول إلى الجبل للتحقيق.
We'll find out soon.
سنكتشف ذلك قريبا.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Didn't I ask you to go to Fengming Pavilion
ألم أطلب منك الذهاب إلى Fengming Pavilion
to buy information from Jin Badou?
لشراء معلومات من جين بادو؟
How did you end up like this?
كيف انتهى بك الحال هكذا؟
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
When we were heading down the mountain, we were ambushed by Wang Di
عندما كنا متجهين إلى أسفل الجبل ، نصبنا وانغ دي كمينًا
before we could find Jin Badou.
قبل أن نجد جين بادو.
He insisted that the Wushan
أصر على أن Wushan
the Black Wind's Double Tyrants stole was fake.
كان سرقة طغاة الريح السوداء المزدوجة مزيفًا.
He even interrogated us about the whereabouts of the real Wushan.
حتى أنه استجوبنا حول مكان وجود ووشان الحقيقي.
Young Master, I'm sorry I failed at my job.
السيد الشاب ، أنا آسف لأنني فشلت في وظيفتي.
This bastard saw through the trick.
رأى هذا اللقيط من خلال الحيلة.
All right.
حسنا.
You two, go back and rest first.
أنتما الاثنان ، عودي واستريحي أولاً.
I'll head down the mountain and look for Jin Badou personally.
سأتوجه إلى الجبل وأبحث عن جين بادو شخصيًا.
-Okay. -Okay.
-تمام.  -تمام.
Li Chengxi, I'll head down the mountain with you.
Li Chengxi ، سأتوجه معك إلى الجبل.
No.
رقم.
Zhi and Ruoyu have just been ambushed.
لقد تم نصب كمين لـ Zhi و Ruoyu.
It's dangerous for you to head down the mountain now.
من الخطر أن تتجه نحو الجبل الآن.
I'm intending to head to Fengming Pavilion
أنا أنوي التوجه إلى Fengming Pavilion
to buy information about the Teardrop Mole people anyway.
لشراء معلومات عن الناس Teardrop Mole على أي حال.
If you don't take me with you, I'll have to go alone.
إذا لم تأخذني معك ، سأضطر للذهاب وحدي.
Wouldn't that be more dangerous?
ألن يكون ذلك أكثر خطورة؟
You lunatic.
أنت مجنون.
What are you doing to me?
ماذا تفعل بي؟
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
You lunatic, let go of me!
أنت مجنون ، اتركني!
I made a mistake.
لقد ارتكبت خطأ.
A mistake?
خطأ؟
I was going to pierce the Baihui acupoint.
كنت على وشك اختراق نقطة الوخز بايهوي.
Why did I pierce the Brain acupoint?
لماذا اخترقت نقطة الوخز في الدماغ؟
This...
هذه...
It's the alcohol's fault.
إنه خطأ الكحول.
What will happen to me now?
ماذا سيحدث لي الآن؟
Don't worry. Nothing will happen.
لا تقلق.  لن يحدث شيء.
The Baihui acupoint can enhance your hearing and sight.
يمكن لنقطة الوخز Baihui تحسين السمع والبصر.
The Brain acupoint
نقطة الوخز الدماغية
can make you delirious,
يمكن أن تجعلك الهذيان ،
foam at the mouth,
رغوة في الفم ،
and paralyze your brain.
وشل عقلك.
It's okay. It's useless for you to have a brain anyway.
انه بخير.  من غير المجدي أن يكون لديك دماغ على أي حال.
You...
أنت...
It seems that I did pierce the right acupoint.
يبدو أنني اخترقت نقطة الوخز الصحيحة.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes, I saw it wrongly.
نعم ، لقد رأيت ذلك بشكل خاطئ.
It's all your fault.
هذا كله خطأك.
Stop staring at me.
توقف عن التحديق في.
I get nervous when you stare at me.
أشعر بالتوتر عندما تحدق في وجهي.
My hands tremble when I'm nervous.
ترتجف يدي عندما أكون متوترة.
Then, it becomes easy to make mistakes.
بعد ذلك ، يصبح من السهل ارتكاب الأخطاء.
I forgot to tell you.
نسيت أن أخبرك.
I just pierced 49 of your acupoints.
لقد اخترقت للتو 49 نقطة من نقاط الوخز الخاصة بك.
That's my own special technique, the Ultimate Seven Steps of...
هذه هي أسلوبي الخاص ، الخطوات السبع المطلقة لـ ...
Death.
موت.
I think I've already taken six steps.
أعتقد أنني اتخذت بالفعل ست خطوات.
So if you take another step,
لذلك إذا اتخذت خطوة أخرى ،
you'll bleed from all 7 orifices.
سوف تنزف من جميع الفتحات السبعة.
Bleed from all 7 orifices?
هل ينزف من جميع الفتحات السبعة؟
You'll be dead.
سوف تموت.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
You lunatic!
أنت مجنون!
Help me fix this.
ساعدني في إصلاح هذا.
You're not allowed to leave, you lunatic!
لا يسمح لك بالمغادرة أيها المجنون!
Watch out!
احذر!
Tang Buyan.
تانغ بويان.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Let me take you to treat your wound.
دعني آخذك لمعالجة جرحك.
Miss Tang!
ملكة جمال تانغ!
Pardon me.
اعذرني.
It hurts.
هذا مؤلم.
It's so hot.
انه حار جدا.
Let go of me.
ترك لي.
Senior sister, I'm training.
الأخت الكبرى ، أنا أتدرب.
Yan.
يان.
Senior sister, I'm tired from the training.
الأخت الكبرى ، لقد تعبت من التدريب.
Can I stop training?
هل يمكنني التوقف عن التدريب؟
Okay.
تمام.
If you're tired,
إذا كنت متعبًا ،
you don't have to train.
ليس عليك التدريب.
Senior sister,
الاخت الكبرى ،
you haven't hugged me in a long time.
لم تعانقني منذ وقت طويل.
♫The east wind blows through calm and good times♫
الريح الشرقية تهب في السكون والطيب ♫
♫Making ripples♫
♫ عمل تموجات ♫
Senior sister, your hug is so warm.
الأخت الكبرى ، عناقك دافئ جدًا.
♫Your poetic face♫
♫ وجهك الشعري ♫
♫Reflects between the lines♫
يعكس ما بين السطور ♫
♫Engraves in my heart♫
يحفر في قلبي ♫
♫The story unlocks a new chapter♫
♫ القصة تفتح فصل جديد ♫
♫Petals meet butterflies♫
♫ بتلات تلتقي بالفراشات
Be good, Yan.
كن جيدًا ، يان.
Go to sleep.
اذهب إلى النوم.
♫Rain or shine♫
♫ ممطر أو مشمس
♫Apex or abyss♫
♫ قمة أم هاوية ♫
Sleep now.
نم حالا.
♫It's all wonderful♫
♫ كل شيء رائع ♫
♫No matter how many light years apart♫
♫ بغض النظر عن عدد السنوات الضوئية التي تفصل بينها ♫
♫It's never too far♫
♫ ليس بعيدًا أبدًا
♫I'll make it to our dates♫
♫ سأصل إلى مواعيدنا ♫
♫Capes and horizons♫
♫ الرؤوس والآفاق ♫
♫When our fingertips touch♫
♫ عندما تلمس أطراف أصابعنا ♫
I'm so thirsty.
أنا عطشان جدآ.
♫In this very moment♫
♫ في هذه اللحظة بالذات ♫
♫I want to be with you forever♫
♫ اريد ان اكون معك الى الابد ♫
I'm thirsty.
عطشان.
♫Seas and fields♫
♫ البحار والحقول ♫
Water.
ماء.
♫Can't change♫
♫ لا يمكن أن تتغير ♫
♫What I would do for you♫
♫ ماذا سأفعل من أجلك ♫
♫Keep the vow♫
احفظ العهد
♫Let's forget the twists and turns♫
♫ دعنا ننسى التقلبات والمنعطفات ♫
♫Rejoice in our wonderful encounter♫
ابتهج بلقائنا الرائع
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
♫The east wind blows through calm and good times♫
الريح الشرقية تهب في السكون والطيب ♫
♫Making ripples♫
♫ عمل تموجات ♫
♫Your poetic face♫
♫ وجهك الشعري ♫
♫Reflects between the lines♫
يعكس ما بين السطور ♫
♫Engraves in my heart♫
يحفر في قلبي ♫
♫The story unlocks a new chapter♫
♫ القصة تفتح فصل جديد ♫
♫Petals meet butterflies♫
♫ بتلات تلتقي بالفراشات
♫Rain or shine♫
♫ ممطر أو مشمس
♫Apex or abyss♫
♫ قمة أم هاوية ♫
♫It's all wonderful♫
♫ كل شيء رائع ♫
♫No matter how many light years apart♫
♫ بغض النظر عن عدد السنوات الضوئية التي تفصل بينها ♫
♫It's never too far♫
♫ ليس بعيدًا أبدًا
♫I'll make it to our dates♫
♫ سأصل إلى مواعيدنا ♫
♫Capes and horizons♫
♫ الرؤوس والآفاق ♫
♫When our fingertips touch♫
♫ عندما تلمس أطراف أصابعنا ♫
♫In this very moment♫
♫ في هذه اللحظة بالذات ♫
♫I want to be with you forever♫
♫ اريد ان اكون معك الى الابد ♫
♫Seas and fields♫
♫ البحار والحقول ♫
♫Can't change♫
♫ لا يمكن أن تتغير ♫
♫What I would do for you♫
♫ ماذا سأفعل من أجلك ♫
♫Keep the vow♫
احفظ العهد
♫Let's forget the twists and turns♫
♫ دعنا ننسى التقلبات والمنعطفات ♫
♫Rejoice in our wonderful encounter♫
ابتهج بلقائنا الرائع
♫No matter how many light years apart♫
♫ بغض النظر عن عدد السنوات الضوئية التي تفصل بينها ♫
♫It's never too far♫
♫ ليس بعيدًا أبدًا
♫Crossing mountains and seas♫
عبور الجبال والبحار
♫Just to look at you one more time♫
♫ فقط أنظر إليك مرة أخرى
♫Gather every moment into eternity♫
اجمع كل لحظة في الخلود
♫Even if the future is not far away♫
حتى لو لم يكن المستقبل بعيدًا
♫I don't regret a single day♫
♫ لست نادما على يوم واحد ♫
♫Spring flowers and the autumn moon♫
♫ زهور الربيع و قمر الخريف ♫
♫Has never changed♫
♫ لم يتغير أبدًا
♫They've witnessed many meetings and partings♫
♫ لقد شهدوا العديد من الاجتماعات والفراق ♫
♫Let's put aside our bias against fate♫
♫ لنضع جانبًا تحيزنا ضد القدر
♫Rejoice in this rare encounter♫
افرحوا في هذا اللقاء النادر
You...
أنت...
Oh no.
أوه لا.
He was kind enough to treat my wound, yet I hit him.
كان لطيفًا بما يكفي لعلاج جرحي ، لكنني ضربته.
I didn't mean to hit you.
لم أقصد أن أضربك.
Are you feeling unwell?
هل تشعر بتوعك؟
You mean me?
تقصدني أنا؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
This minor injury is nothing to me.
هذه الإصابة الطفيفة ليست شيئا بالنسبة لي.
Let me take you back to Physician Yan first.
دعني أعود بك إلى الطبيب يان أولاً.
I'm really fine.
أنا بخير حقا.
Don't bother Physician Yan for such a trivial matter.
لا تزعج الطبيب يان لمثل هذا الأمر التافه.
I think we should go
أعتقد أننا يجب أن نذهب
look for Jin Badou first.
ابحث عن جين بادو أولاً.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
The physician said your blood vessel disease is progressing faster than expected.
قال الطبيب إن مرض الأوعية الدموية لديك يتقدم بشكل أسرع من المتوقع.
You won't be able to live past 25 years old.
لن تكون قادرًا على العيش بعد 25 عامًا.